Guide to Central Washington University Business and Financial Affairs 2019
Central Washington University Archives and Special Collections
  - Fee Requests, Combined Business Plan, 2004-2011 (Box-folder 31-2)
  - Korea and China Relations, Student Recruitment, 2007- (Box-folder 31-3)
  - Emerging Needs, 2010- (Box-folder 31-4)
  - Budget Process Overview, 2010-2011 (Box-folder 31-5)
  - Enrollment Update, Audits, 2010-2013 (Box-folder 31-6)
  - Net Assets, 2010-2013 (Box-folder 31-7)
  - Tuition Waivers, 2010-2014 (Box-folder 31-8)
  - Albertson's Property, 2011- (Box-folder 31-9)
  - Agreement with Guangxi University, 2011- (Box-folder 31-10)
  - Auxiliary Services Highlights, Newsletter, 2011- (Box-folder 31-11)
  - Endowment Accounts, Balances, 2011- (Box-folder 31-12)
  - B.F.A. BOD Agendas, 2011- (Box-folder 31-13)
  - West Waivers, Update, 2011- (Box-folder 31-14)
  - National Search Committee, 2011-2012 (Box-folder 31-15)
  - Aviation Program Resources, 2012- (Box-folder 31-16)
  - Canedo, Agnes Retirement, 2012- (Box-folder 31-17)
  - BFA Summary, 2012- (Box-folder 31-18)
  - Capital Projects Overview, 2012- (Box-folder 31-19)
  - Capital projects Overview, 2012- (Box-folder 31-20)
  - Community Meeting, 2012- (Box-folder 31-21)
  - Funds Balances, 2012- (Box-folder 31-22)
  - Revenue and Debt, 2012- (Box-folder 31-23)
  - U.S. Bank Portfolio, 2012- (Box-folder 31-24)
  - Capital Projects Evaluation, 2013- (Box-folder 31-25)
  - Budget Overview, 2014-2015 (Box-folder 31-26)
  - Enrollment Management, 2016- (Box-folder 31-27)
  - Parking History Survey, 1995-2008 (Box-folder 32-1)
  - Business Services and Contracts, 1997-2006 (Box-folder 32-2)
  - Summer Session Budgets, 1998-2003 (Box-folder 32-3)
  - Student Capacity, 2000-2004 (Box-folder 32-4)
  - HR, Leave, 2001-2005 (Box-folder 32-5)
  - Facilities Performance, 2001-2007 (Box-folder 32-6)
  - Federal Annual Certificate Interlocal Cooperative Agreement, 2002- (Box-folder 32-7)
  - Kamola Hall Restoration, 2002- (Box-folder 32-8)
  - Sue Lombard Renovation SURC Project, 2002-2003 (Box-folder 32-9)
  - Air Travel, 2003- (Box-folder 32-10)
  - John Wayne Trail Charter Agreement, 2003- (Box-folder 32-11)
  - Tamamura Rose Garden resolution, 2003- (Box-folder 32-12)
  - Insurance Eligibility, 2003-2005 (Box-folder 32-13)
  - Foundation Resource Development, 2004- (Box-folder 32-14)
  - Safe Ride, Survey, 2004- (Box-folder 32-15)
  - Wenatchee Valley Higher Education Center, 2004-2006 (Box-folder 32-16)
  - Tunstall Commons Dining Halls Renovations, 2005- (Box-folder 32-17)
  - Wireless Computing at CWU, 2005- (Box-folder 32-18)
  - Hiring Practices, 2006- (Box-folder 32-19)
  - Parking at 11th and Maple project, 2005- (Box-folder 32-20)
  - Retirement Planning Document, 2006- (Box-folder 32-21)
  - Senate Bill 6420, House Bill 2583, 2006- (Box-folder 32-22)
  - Policy Review, Changes, 2006-2008 (Box-folder 32-23)
  - ASCWU Correspondence, 2007- (Box-folder 32-24)
  - Apoyo, food bank, 2008- (Box-folder 32-25)
  - Budget Priorities, President's Division, 2014- (Box-folder 32-26)
  - Budget Overview, 2014- (Box-folder 32-27)
  - Innovation Fund Program, 2014- (Box-folder 32-28)
  - Operations Budget, 2014- (Box-folder 32-29)
  - Housing System Revenue Bonds, 2002-2012 (Box-folder 33-1)
  - Office of International Studies Program, 2010- (Box-folder 33-2)
  - Munson Hall, 2010- (Box-folder 33-3)
  - Metric, 2010- (Box-folder 33-4)
  - Public Records Request, 2011- (Box-folder 33-5)
  - Private Student Loan Program, 2011- (Box-folder 33-6)
  - Parking Lot Price Comparison, 2011- (Box-folder 33-7)
  - Public Centralized Higher Education Enrollment System, 2011- (Box-folder 33-8)
  - Indirect Cost Distribution, 2011- (Box-folder 33-9)
  - Ombudsman Association, 2011- (Box-folder 33-10)
  - Police Chief, 2011- (Box-folder 33-11)
  - Landscape Maintenance, 2011- (Box-folder 33-12)
  - Reorganization, 2011- (Box-folder 33-13)
  - Right Size Support for CWU Enterprise Systems and Strategic Initiatives, 2011-2012 (Box-folder 33-14)
  - Responsibility Centered Management, 2011-2012 (Box-folder 33-15)
  - S and A Fee Fund, 2011-2014 (Box-folder 33-16)
  - Risk Assessment, 2012- (Box-folder 33-17)
  - Lease, 2012- (Box-folder 33-18)
  - Medical Clinic, 2012- (Box-folder 33-19)
  - Campus Maps, 2012- (Box-folder 33-20)
  - Retirement Redesign Update, 2012- (Box-folder 33-21)
  - Science Neighborhood Capital Project, 2012- (Box-folder 33-22)
  - Information Services Project Plan, 2012-2013 (Box-folder 33-23)
  - Minor Works, 2013- (Box-folder 33-24)
  - ICAT, EM, OE, IR, 2013- (Box-folder 33-25)
  - Peterson Hall, 2014- (Box-folder 33-26)
  - Awards Ceremony, 2015- (Box-folder 33-27)
  - Lease Purchase Financing, 1998-1999 (Box-folder 34-1)
  - President's Cabinet Retreat, 2001- (Box-folder 34-2)
  - Cabinet Retreat, 2002- (Box-folder 34-3)
  - Cabinet Retreat, 2003- (Box-folder 34-4)
  - Travel, 2003-2004 (Box-folder 34-5)
  - Cabinet Retreat, 2004-2005 (Box-folder 34-6)
  - Cabinet Retreat, 2005- (Box-folder 34-7)
  - Operating Budget Requests, 2006- (Box-folder 34-8)
  - Emergency, Pollution Plans, 1998- (Box-folder 35-1)
  - Center for Excellence and Leadership Proposal, 1998- (Box-folder 35-2)
  - Residence Hall transformation, 2001- (Box-folder 35-3)
  - Audits Exit and Entrance Conferences, 2001-2008 (Box-folder 35-4)
  - External Grant and Contract Activities, 2002-2003 (Box-folder 35-5)
  - House Education Finance, 2005-2006 (Box-folder 35-6)
  - Auxiliary Business Plan, 2005-2006 (Box-folder 35-7)
  - Council of Presidents, Priorities List, 2007- (Box-folder 35-8)
  - Math and Writing Centers, 2007- (Box-folder 35-9)
  - CWU Economic Impact, 2007-2008 (Box-folder 35-10)
  - Courson and Muzzall Hall Removal, 2008- (Box-folder 35-11)
  - Corona, Rich Correspondence, 2008- (Box-folder 35-12)
  - Admin Fees, 2009- (Box-folder 35-13)
  - Declaration of Emergency, 2009- (Box-folder 35-14)
  - Gladmar Advisory Committee Agenda, 2009- (Box-folder 35-15)
  - Rental Fees, 2009- (Box-folder 35-16)
  - Secretary Pay, 2009-2010 (Box-folder 35-17)
  - Athletics Department Funding, 2009-2011 (Box-folder 35-18)
  - Budgeting, Accounting and Reporting, 2011- (Box-folder 35-19)
  - President's Advisory Council, 2004- (Box-folder 36-1)
  - President's Cabinet, 2004- (Box-folder 36-2)
  - CWU History, 2005- (Box-folder 36-3)
  - President's Cabinet Agenda, 2005- (Box-folder 36-4)
  - President's Advisory Council, 2005-2006 (Box-folder 36-5)
  - Integrated Planning, 2006- (Box-folder 36-6)
  - President's Cabinet, 2006- (Box-folder 36-7)
  - President's Cabinet Minutes, 2006- (Box-folder 36-8)
  - Reassignment, 2010- (Box-folder 36-9)
  - CWU Enterprise, 2011- (Box-folder 36-10)
  - Organizational Update, 2011- (Box-folder 36-11)
  - Boiler Stack Heat Recovery, 2013- (Box-folder 36-12)
  - Presidential Leadership Team, 2013- (Box-folder 36-13)
  - Planning, Budgeting and Forecasting Review McGladrey Audit, 2014- (Box-folder 36-14)
  - Payroll Data Management Task Force, 2014- (Box-folder 36-15)
  - Cash Management, 1994-2004 (Box-folder 37-1)
  - Tax ID Number Requirement, 1997- (Box-folder 37-2)
  - IRS, 1992- (Box-folder 37-3)
  - Conference Program, 1997-2005 (Box-folder 37-4)
  - State Treasure, 1998-2003 (Box-folder 37-5)
  - Tuition Waivers, Athletic Scholarship program, 1998-2005 (Box-folder 37-6)
  - Economic Impact of CWU on Kittitas County, 2000-2002 (Box-folder 37-7)
  - Document Retention and Destruction, 2000-2007 (Box-folder 37-8)
  - Travel Performance Evaluation, 2001- (Box-folder 37-9)
  - Service Vehicles on Campus, 2001-2003 (Box-folder 37-10)
  - Tuition and Fee Dispersal, 2001-2006 (Box-folder 37-11)
  - State Investment Board, 2002-2003 (Box-folder 37-12)
  - Chart of Accounts, 2002-2006 (Box-folder 37-13)
  - Quarter Tuition and Fees for Regular Session, 2002-2007 (Box-folder 37-14)
  - Athletics Department Budget, 2003- (Box-folder 37-15)
  - Campus Safety Committee, 2003- (Box-folder 37-16)
  - Department of Natural Resources, 2003- (Box-folder 37-17)
  - CWU Centers, 2003-2005 (Box-folder 37-18)
  - Budgeting, Accounting and Reporting, 2003-2007 (Box-folder 37-19)
  - Enterprise Information Systems Governance at CWU, Finance Upgrade Project, 2004- (Box-folder 37-20)
  - Exempt Employee Association, 2005- (Box-folder 37-21)
  - Operating Budget Requests, 2005-2006 (Box-folder 37-22)
  - Communication Assistance for Law Enforcement Act, 2006- (Box-folder 37-23)
  - Payroll Changes, 2006- (Box-folder 37-24)
  - Lease Hold Excise tax, 2006- (Box-folder 37-25)
  - Employee Appreciation Program, 2007- (Box-folder 37-26)
  - Director of Accounting Search Committee, 2007- (Box-folder 37-27)
  - Unclaimed Property, 2007- (Box-folder 37-28)
  - Identity Theft Prevention Conference, 2008- (Box-folder 37-29)
  - NACUBO, 2008- (Box-folder 37-30)
  - Updated and Appraisal on Purchased Property, 2008- (Box-folder 37-31)
  - Tuition and Fee Distribution, 2008-2009 (Box-folder 37-32)
  - Washington State Auditor, 2009- (Box-folder 37-33)
  - Fee List, 2005-2007 (Box-folder 38-1)
  - Administrative Allowance, 2000-2004 (Box-folder 38-2)
  - Contracting Out, 2003- (Box-folder 38-3)
  - Procedure for Promotional Expenditures, 2007-2008 (Box-folder 38-4)
  - Investment Interest Report, 2008- (Box-folder 38-5)
  - Unit Reports, 2008-2010 (Box-folder 38-6)
  - Collective Bargaining Agreement, 2009- (Box-folder 38-7)
  - Initial Allocations, 2009- (Box-folder 38-8)
  - Beginning Allocations, 2009-2010 (Box-folder 38-9)
  - Beginning Allocations part 2, 2009-2010 (Box-folder 38-10)
  - CWU Foundation, Statements, Agreements, 1968-1998 (Box-folder 39-1)
  - Appropriate Expenditures, 1970-1990 (Box-folder 39-2)
  - Economic Impact of CWU, 1973-1984 (Box-folder 39-3)
  - Recharge and Physical plant Work Force Information, 1989-1993 (Box-folder 39-4)
  - Admin Charge, 1983-2006 (Box-folder 39-5)
  - Facilities Management Smoking/Nonsmoking Survey, 1985-1987 (Box-folder 39-6)
  - Admissions Tax, 1988-1990 (Box-folder 39-7)
  - Public Trust Lands, 1989-2004 (Box-folder 39-8)
  - State Archivist Letters, 1989-1994 (Box-folder 39-9)
  - Ware Fair, Business License, Budget, 1991- (Box-folder 39-10)
  - SMK Mechanical, Incorporated vs. Pacific Crest-CWU, 1993- (Box-folder 39-11)
  - Chamber of Commerce Correspondence, 1993- (Box-folder 39-12)
  - Unified Personnel System Committee, Cleaning Fees, 1993- (Box-folder 39-13)
  - Legislative Correspondence, 1990- (Box-folder 39-14)
  - Legislative Labor Relations, Committees, 1991- (Box-folder 39-15)
  - Policy on Debts, 1991-2001 (Box-folder 39-16)
  - Old Fund 149 Revenues, 1994- (Box-folder 39-17)
  - CWU Economic Impact, 1994-2000 (Box-folder 39-18)
  - Washington Higher Education Network Proposal, 1995- (Box-folder 39-19)
  - Student Capacity in Facilities, 1995- (Box-folder 39-20)
  - Supplemental Budget Request, 1996- (Box-folder 39-21)
  - Submitted Documents, 1993- (Box-folder 40-1)
  - Incident Letter, 1993-1994 (Box-folder 40-2)
  - HB Painters Incorporated v. State of Washington, 1993-1996 (Box-folder 40-3)
  - Claim: Mike's Rental Machinery, 1993-1997 (Box-folder 40-4)
  - Building Construction Moratorium, 1994- (Box-folder 40-5)
  - Science Building Planning, 1994- (Box-folder 40-6)
  - Staff Agenda Minutes, 1994- (Box-folder 40-7)
  - Erikson, Frank Complaint Documents, 1994- (Box-folder 40-8)
  - Public Meetings Parking, 1994-1995 (Box-folder 40-9)
  - Student Financial Assistance Programs, 1994-1996 (Box-folder 40-10)
  - Nasser, Abdul V.P. Reader File, 1994-1997 (Box-folder 40-11)
  - Central Services and Auxiliary Merger Understandings, 1995- (Box-folder 40-12)
  - Chamber of Commerce leadership Training Program, 1995- (Box-folder 40-13)
  - Interlocal Agreement, 1995- (Box-folder 40-14)
  - Compliance, UESL Program, 1995- (Box-folder 40-15)
  - President's Cabinet, E-mails, 1995- (Box-folder 40-16)
  - Staff Agenda, Minutes, 1995- (Box-folder 40-17)
  - Actor's Equity Association, 1996- (Box-folder 40-18)
  - Training and Committee Development, 1998-2001 (Box-folder 40-19)
  - Enterprise Information Systems, 2001-2002 (Box-folder 41-1)
  - Budget Cuts, Reports, Notes, 2001-2003 (Box-folder 41-2)
  - Reallocation of Funds, People Soft Implementation, 2001-2002 (Box-folder 41-3)
  - ASSP Administrative Support Systems Project, 2002- (Box-folder 41-4)
  - Grant Process, 145, 148 Funds, 1987-1989 (Box-folder 41-5)
  - Student Financial Service, Annual Evaluation, 1994-1995 (Box-folder 41-6)
  - Running Start, 1994-1996 (Box-folder 41-7)
  - Coca Cola Scholarship Fund, 1994-1999 (Box-folder 41-8)
  - Budget Advisory Committee, Minutes, 1996- (Box-folder 41-9)
  - Annual Evaluation, Response, 1996- (Box-folder 41-10)
  - Electronic Funds Transfer, 1996- (Box-folder 41-11)
  - Annual Evaluation, Responses to Questions, 1997- (Box-folder 41-12)
  - Budget Advisory Committee, Minutes, 1997- (Box-folder 41-13)
  - Annual Evaluation, Response, 1998- (Box-folder 41-14)
  - Annual Evaluation Response, 1999- (Box-folder 41-15)
  - Budget Advisory Committee, Minutes, 1999- (Box-folder 41-16)
  - Annual Evaluation, Student Financial Services, 2000- (Box-folder 41-17)
  - Annual Performance Evaluation, 2001- (Box-folder 41-18)
  - Budget Advisory Committee, Minutes, 2001- (Box-folder 41-19)
  - Services and activities Committee, 2001- (Box-folder 41-20)
  - Local Government Investment, 2001- (Box-folder 41-21)
  - Budget Advisory Committee, Minutes, 2002- (Box-folder 41-22)
  - Performance Evaluation, 2002- (Box-folder 41-23)
  - Washington State Archives, 1995-2011 (Box-folder 42-1)
  - Revenue Bond refunds, 2002-2011 (Box-folder 42-2)
  - Business and Financial Affairs Retreat, 2004-2006 (Box-folder 42-3)
  - HR, 2004-2011 (Box-folder 42-4)
  - CWU Research Foundation, Conflict of Interest, 2008- (Box-folder 42-5)
  - Academic Planning Task Force, 2009- (Box-folder 42-6)
  - Wildcat Wheels Courtesy Car Programs, 2009- (Box-folder 42-7)
  - Student Employment Stats, 2009-2010 (Box-folder 42-8)
  - Provost Council, 2009-2011 (Box-folder 42-9)
  - Bank Accounts, 2010- (Box-folder 42-10)
  - Association of Governing Boards of Universities, 2007-2011 (Box-folder 42-11)
  - Associate V.P. Financial Services, 2011- (Box-folder 42-12)
  - Board of Directors, Executive Briefing, 2011- (Box-folder 42-13)
  - Board of Trustees, Meeting, 2011- (Box-folder 42-14)
  - Focus Group, Chimpanzee Human Communication Institute, Lynwood, Wine Program, 2011- (Box-folder 42-15)
  - President's Advisory Council, 2011- (Box-folder 42-16)
  - Minor Works Program, 2011- (Box-folder 42-17)
  - Student Accounts, 2011-2012 (Box-folder 42-18)
  - Foundation, Contract, Budget, 1991-1993 (Box-folder 43-1)
  - Foundation, Report, Audits, 1996-1997 (Box-folder 43-2)
  - Foundation, Financial Position, 1997-1998 (Box-folder 43-3)
  - Foundation Reports, 1998-1999 (Box-folder 43-4)
  - Foundation, Audit Report, 2000-2007 (Box-folder 43-5)
  - Foundation Agreement, U.S. Bank Portfolio, 2008-2009 (Box-folder 43-6)
  - New Barto Hall, 2008-2010 (Box-folder 43-7)
  - CWU Research Foundation, Policies, Minutes, -2011 (Box-folder 43-8)
  - Public Private Partnerships, 2009- (Box-folder 43-9)
  - Budget Projections Correspondence, 2009- (Box-folder 43-10)
  - Sponsors, Purchasing, Belt Tightening, 2009-2010 (Box-folder 43-11)
  - Post Issuance Procedures for Tax Advantaged Bonds, 2010- (Box-folder 43-12)
  - Retirement and Insurance Committee, 2010- (Box-folder 43-13)
  - Independent Audit Report, 2003-2004 (Box-folder 44-1)
  - Independent Audit Report, 2004-2005 (Box-folder 44-2)
  - Independent Audit Report, 2005-2006 (Box-folder 44-3)
  - Independent Audit Report, 2006-2007 (Box-folder 44-4)
  - Systems Control Operations Risk Evaluation, 2007- (Box-folder 44-5)
  - Business Affairs Council, 2008- (Box-folder 44-6)
  - CWU Research Foundation, Policies, Minutes, 2008- (Box-folder 44-7)
  - University Relations, 2008- (Box-folder 44-8)
  - Business Affairs Council, 2009- (Box-folder 44-9)
  - Capital Budgets Requests, 2010- (Box-folder 44-10)
  - Business Affairs Council, Task Force, 2011- (Box-folder 44-11)
  - Cabinet Meeting Agendas, 2011- (Box-folder 44-12)
  - Enrollment Management, 2011- (Box-folder 44-13)
  - Budget Advisory Committee, Minutes, 1999- (Box-folder 45-1)
  - Program Review, Budget Reports, Notes, Correspondence, 1999-2000 (Box-folder 45-2)
  - Auxiliary Projects, BOT Briefs, budgets, 1999-2001 (Box-folder 45-3)
  - Budget Advisory Committee, Minutes, 2000- (Box-folder 45-4)
  - Budget Reduction Policies, 2001- (Box-folder 45-5)
  - Kamola Hall Bonds, Insurance, 2001-2002 (Box-folder 45-6)
  - Budget Advisory Committee, Minutes, 2002-2003 (Box-folder 45-7)
  - CWU's Relationship's with the Yakama Nation and Hispanic Community Since 2000 (Box-folder 45-8)
  - Higher Education Coordinating Board, State Fee Schedule, 2002- (Box-folder 45-9)
  - Parking and Conference Program, 1987-1992 (Box-folder 46-1)
  - Steam Chilled Water Study: Dean hall Kamola, 1997- (Box-folder 46-2)
  - Athletics Camps Funds, 1997-2004 (Box-folder 46-3)
  - Cancellation Swimming, Wrestling Teams, 2003-2004 (Box-folder 46-4)
  - Review of Athletic budget, 2002-2003 (Box-folder 46-5)
  - Athletics Budget, reports, Correspondence, Scoreboard, 2004-2008 (Box-folder 46-6)
  - Athletic Department Budget VI, VII, Schactler Management Strategies, 2004- (Box-folder 46-7)
  - Athletic Department Budget, 2005- (Box-folder 46-8)
  - Athletics Budget Summary, 2007- (Box-folder 46-9)
  - Athletics Budget Summary, 2006- (Box-folder 46-10)
  - Budget Project Summary for Athletics, 2008- (Box-folder 46-11)
  - Fire Protection Agreement Between CWU and Ellensburg, 1994-1997 (Box-folder 47-1)
  - Budget Hearings, Reports, 1996-2000 (Box-folder 47-2)
  - Campus Facilities, Repairs, 1998- (Box-folder 47-3)
  - Budget Priorities, 1999-2000 (Box-folder 47-4)
  - Fee Schedule, Correspondence, 2001-2005 (Box-folder 47-5)
  - Child Care on Campus, Head Start, 2002- (Box-folder 47-6)
  - Services and Activities Committee, 2002- (Box-folder 47-7)
  - Base Budget Information, 2003-2004 (Box-folder 47-8)
  - Salary Savings, 2003-2005 (Box-folder 47-9)
  - Committee Appointments, 1979-1989 (Box-folder 48-1)
  - Appointment of Committee Members, 1990-1998 (Box-folder 48-2)
  - Regular Interim Report, Recommendations from Accreditation Visit, Responses, 1994-2004 (Box-folder 48-3)
  - Members, Duties and Responsibilities of Strategic Planning Committee, 1995-1996 (Box-folder 48-4)
  - College of Business Coordinated Planning Packet, 1996- (Box-folder 48-5)
  - Reorganization of Auxiliary Services, 1996-1997 (Box-folder 48-6)
  - Strategic Plan for Business and Financial Affairs, 1996-2001 (Box-folder 48-7)
  - Strategic Plan for Business and Financial Affairs, 1998-2001 (Box-folder 48-8)
  - Small Town Institute, Correspondence, 2000- (Box-folder 48-9)
  - Connection Card, Policies, 2003-2008 (Box-folder 49-1)
  - Annual Evaluation, 2004- (Box-folder 49-2)
  - Annual Evaluation, 2005- (Box-folder 49-3)
  - Space Assignment Detail, 2005- (Box-folder 49-4)
  - Council of Presidents, Agenda, Notes, 2005-2006 (Box-folder 49-5)
  - Identity Theft, 2008- (Box-folder 49-6)
  - Recruitment Package, 2006-2007 (Box-folder 49-7)
  - Campus Site and Development Committee, 2006-2007 (Box-folder 49-8)
  - Capital Budget Overview, 2004- (Box-folder 49-9)
  - Capital Project Funds, 2007- (Box-folder 49-10)
  - Legislative Budget Request, 2007-2009 (Box-folder 49-11)
  - Budget, 2009 (Box-folder 49-12)
  - ProCard purchase log, 2008- (Box-folder 49-13)
  - Budget Driver, 2009- (Box-folder 49-14)
  - Capital Budget Committee Annual Report, 2009- (Box-folder 49-15)
  - Campus Safety and Health Committee, 2009- (Box-folder 49-16)
  - Impact of State Budget Cuts, 2009- (Box-folder 49-17)
  - Biomass Fueled Combined Heat and Power Feasibility Study, Final Report, 2010- (Box-folder 49-18)
  - Capital Projects, 2010- (Box-folder 49-19)
  - Budget Reduction Scenario, 2010- (Box-folder 49-20)
  - Facilities Management Risk Factors of Unfilled Positions, 2010- (Box-folder 49-21)
  - Salary Savings Requests, 2010- (Box-folder 49-22)
  - Auxiliary Budgeting and Reporting, 2013- (Box-folder 49-23)
  - Whistleblower Report, 1998-1999 (Box-folder 50-1)
  - Employee Training and Development, 1997-2000 (Box-folder 50-2)
  - Statement of CWU Foundation Financial Position, Activities, 2004- (Box-folder 50 -3)
  - CWU Foundation Independent Auditor's Report, 2004-2005 (Box-folder 50-4)
  - CWU Investment Review, 2005- (Box-folder 50-5)
  - Independent Auditor's Report, CWU Foundation, 2005-2006 (Box-folder 50-6)
  - CWU Investments Review, 2006- (Box-folder 50-7)
  - CWU President Position Description, 2008- (Box-folder 50-8)
  - Business Affairs Committees, Minutes, 2008-2009 (Box-folder 50-9)
  - Financial Affairs Department, Overview, 2008-2011 (Box-folder 50-10)
  - Grants and Contracts Revenue Reports, 2008-2011 (Box-folder 50-11)
  - Board of Trustees Agenda Items, 2009- (Box-folder 50-12)
  - Resource Development and Audit Committee Meeting Minutes, 2009- (Box-folder 50-13)
  - Council of Presidents Interlocal Cooperation Agreement, 2009-2011 (Box-folder 50-14)
  - Consolidation of Custodial Services, 2010- (Box-folder 50-15)
  - CWU Foundation Portfolio Report, 2010-2011 (Box-folder 50-16)
  - Profit Recovery Services, Business Documents Review, Engagement Review, 1999- (Box-folder 51-1)
  - CWU Foundation Report, 2003- (Box-folder 51-2)
  - CWU Dining Services, Summary, 2004-2005 (Box-folder 51-3)
  - Dining Services Financial Report, 2005-2008 (Box-folder 51-4)
  - Administrative Fee, 2005-2006 (Box-folder 51-5)
  - Cell Phone Policy, 2007-2008 (Box-folder 51-6)
  - GFOA, GAAP Conference, 2007-2008 (Box-folder 51-7)
  - Unaudited Net Assets, 2008-2009 (Box-folder 51-8)
  - CWURF Presentation, 2008-2011 (Box-folder 51-9)
  - New Residence Hall, 2009- (Box-folder 51-10)
  - Accountability Audit Report, 2009-2010 (Box-folder 51-11)
  - Audit Findings and Responses, 2009-2010 (Box-folder 51-12)
  - CWU Bond Finance Plan, 2009-2010 (Box-folder 51-13)
  - Benefits Plan, Auditor's Report, 2009-2011 (Box-folder 51-14)
  - CWU Foundation Investment and Finance Committee, 2009-2012 (Box-folder 51-15)
  - CWU Tuition and Fees Comparison, 2010-2011 (Box-folder 51-16)
  - Voluntary Incentive program, Hiring freeze, 2010-2011 (Box-folder 51-17)
  - Leave Agreement, Ya Yun Music College, 1968-2003 (Box-folder 52-1)
  - Procedures, Administrative, 1970-2000 (Box-folder 52-2)
  - Ethical Discussions, Correspondence, 1977-1996 (Box-folder 52-3)
  - Club Accounts, Investments, 1990-1996 (Box-folder 52-4)
  - Faculty and Staff, 1996-1999 (Box-folder 52-5)
  - SURC Admission Tax, Budget, 2004-2010 (Box-folder 52-6)
  - Payment Card Industry, Security, 2005-2009 (Box-folder 52-7)
  - Unrelated Business Income tax, 2005-2011 (Box-folder 52-8)
  - Emergency Services, 1996-2005 (Box-folder 53-1)
  - Vice President Business Advisory Council, 2001-2003 (Box-folder 53-2)
  - Meeting Notes, 2001-2004 (Box-folder 53-3)
  - President's Advisory Cabinet, 2005- (Box-folder 53-4)
  - Campus Development, 2005- (Box-folder 53-5)
  - Campus Development, 2005- (Box-folder 53-6)
  - Business Advisory Committee, 2006- (Box-folder 53-7)
  - Bill Ventrees Meeting Notes, 2006- (Box-folder 53-8)
  - Payroll, 2006- (Box-folder 53-9)
  - Steve Ritterser notes, 2006- (Box-folder 53-10)
  - Ellensburg Correspondence, 2007- (Box-folder 53-11)
  - President's Cabinet, 2007- (Box-folder 53-12)
  - Project Notes, 2007- (Box-folder 53-13)
  - Central Stores, Response to Audit Recommendations, 1984- (Box-folder 54-1)
  - Legislative Action Committee, 1991-1993 (Box-folder 54-2)
  - Corona, Richard Reader File, 1993-1994 (Box-folder 54-3)
  - Internal Audit, 1994- (Box-folder 54-4)
  - Corona, Richard Reader File, 1994-1995 (Box-folder 54-5)
  - Examination of Facilities manager, 1996- (Box-folder 54-6)